Guide to the Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Photographs, 1914-present CTC.1966.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Productions, 1938-2011; I.; 1021.0 photographs
  - Life with Mother, 1994; 1.0 photograph
    Life with Mother was presented by Mountain Playhouse from July 12-24, 1994. Photograph is of Adam Bryant and Matt Bryant.
  - Light Up the Sky, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    Light Up the Sky was presented by the White Barn Theatre from June 15-26, 1976. Photograph is of Ginny Heller and Carol DePaul.
  - Light Up the Sky - Mattress Factory, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the Mattress Factory's production of Light Up the Sky including Dean Hyland, Johnette Sullivan, and Joan Kimmel.
  - A Lion in Winter, 1989; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is a scene from A Lion in Winter. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed in 1989.
  - Lips Together, Teeth Apart, 1994; 1.0 photograph
    Lips Together, Teeth Apart was presented by City Theatre from January 14 - February 6, 1994. Photograph is of Helena Ruoti and Scott Baron.
  - A Little Night Music - Carnegie Mellon University, 1989; 1.0 photograph
    A Little Night Music was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from February 15 - March 4, 1989 at the Kresge Theatre. This photograph is of Maria Sneden and Jack Plotnick.
  - A Little Night Music - Plaza Theatre, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    A Little Night Music was presented by Camelot Productions from September 24 - October 17, 1976 at the Plaza Theatre. This photograph is of Barbara Fuchs and Norma Thomas.
  - Little Rock, 1.0 photograph
    Little Rock was presented by the Saltworks Theatre Company. The photograph is of Jordan Mueller and Faith R. Rodman and is undated.
  - Little Shop of Horrors - Apple Hill Playhouse, 1.0 photograph
    Little Shop of Horrors was presented by the Apple Hill Playhouse. Photograph is of John Carosella (director), Jenny O'Hara, J. Rob Springer, and Bruce Robinson.
  - Little Shop of Horrors - Mountain Playhouse, July 1996; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Tamara Baron and Jase Draper. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from July 9 - 21, 1996.
  - Living Together, Dec. 1980; 7.0 photographs
    This folder contains the Winter Company's production of Living Together. The first photo includes Ruth Lesko and Charles Altman. The second photo includes Natalie Baker, Maura Minteer, and Ruth Lesko. The third is of Maura Minteer. The fourth is of David Butler. The fifth is of Ken Milchick and Natalie Baker. The sixth and seventh is of Ken Milchick.
  - Lone Star, 1981; 2.0 photographs
    These photographs shows cast members of Lone Star. Included in the photos are Robert Koch, Tom Lehner, and Thomas C. Haley IV. The Fine Line Theatre Company play was performed along with the play Pvt. Wars at the Soho Theatre in Oakland May 29th through June 21st, 1981.
  - Loot, 1979-1980; 1.0 photograph
    Loot was presented by the Pittsburgh Public Theater from December 27, 1979 - February 10, 1980. Photograph is of David Rotenber (Director) and John Carpenter.
  - Lost in Yonkers, 1996; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Paul M. Tresnicky, David L. Gilbert, and Margaret Goodman. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from August 20 - September 1, 1996.
  - Love, Sex, and the I.R.S., 1991; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Michael McCarty, Joe Muzikar, and David Garwood. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed in 1991.
  - Lucky Stiff, 1998; 1.0 photograph
    Lucky Stiff was presented by Mountain Playhouse from August 4-16, 1998. Cast members pictured are Nick Ruggeri, Amy D. Forbes, Will Gartshore, Janet Dickinson, Jase Draper, and David Garwood.
  - Luv - Allegheny Repertory Theatre, 1983; 2.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Patricia M. Stack and Mark Tierno. This production was performed by the Allegheny Repertory Theatre at the Famous Rider Cultural Center from April 15th through May 8th, 1983.
  - Luv - The Cabaret Theatre, Hempfield, 1980/81; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the Cabaret Theatre's production of Luv.
  - Luv - Fort Pitt Inn Dinner Theatre, 1982; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Fort Pitt Inn Dinner Theatre's Production of Luv including Frank Mitolo and Ed Sipes.
  - Luv - Robert Morris College, 1978; 1.0 photograph
    Luv was presented by Robert Morris College Colonial Theater from August 10-10, 1978. Photograph is of Marcia Harenski.
  - A Lyrical Christmas Carol, 3.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Jim Critchfield and Elizabeth Vitalbo. A Lyrical Christmas Carol is a Gargaro Productions. This performance was held at the Antonian Theater.
  - Machinal, 1999; 1.0 photograph
    Machinal was presented by the City Theatre from March 3-21, 1999. Photograph is of Jim Cook and Laura Smiley.
  - Madanabadha, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Holly Ricciuti and Michael Lovice. This University of Pittsburgh Theatre production was performed at the Pit Theatre in Oakland.
  - Made By Two, 1979; 4.0 photographs
    Made By Two was presented by Theatre Express from March 8 - April 1, 1979. Photographs are of cast members Joan Kimmel, Susan Cash, and Catherine Roberts.
  - Made By Two, 1980; 1.0 photograph
    Made By Two was presented by Theatre Express from April 3-20, 1980. Photograph is of cast members Claudia Zahn, Eleanor Glockner, and Janet Reed.
  - Makin' Whoopee, 1981; 2.0 photographs
    Makin' Whoopee was presented at the Stanley Theatre from February 10-15,1981. Photographs are of cast members Paul Elkin, Billy Rowley, Ted Pritchard, and Frank Silvano.
  - The Making of Americans, 1981; 3.0 photographs
    The Making of Americans was presented by the Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from September 5-28, 1980. Photographs are of Robin Grattan, Robin Walsh, Ian Gallacher (Co-Musical Director), and David Miller (Composer).
  - Mame, 1994; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Nancy Dussault. This Civic Light Opera production was performed in 1994 at the Benedum Center.
  - Man in the Dog Suit, 1959; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Bob Riehl, Augusta Steele, and John M. Simpson. This production was performed at the Pittsburgh Playhouse. Photograph is dated June 28, 1959.
  - The Man in the Glass Booth, 1983; 2.0 photographs
    The Man in the Glass Booth was presented by the Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from January 14 - February 13, 1983. Photographs are of Bingo O'Malley and Jack Price.
  - Man of La Mancha - Community College of Allegheny College, 1980; 2.0 photographs
    Man of La Mancha was presented by the Community College of Allegheny County from July 10-26, 1980. Photographs are of Terry Azzara, Michael Wieser, Joe Clement, John Truby, and Blair Wojton.
  - The Man Who Lived Underground, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    The Man Who Lived Underground was presented by City Theatre from May 26 - June 20, 1993. Photograph is of Don Marshall.
  - The Man Who Turned Into a Stick, February 1993; 1.0 photograph
    This photograph shows actors Eddie Manley and Lisa Pittek. The Man Who Turned Into a Stick was part of the 10th year of Community College of Allegheny County's New Director's Series. The play was performed at the Boyce campus during February 24-27, 1993.
  - The Mandrake, 1973; 1.0 photograph
    The Mandrake was presented by the Pittsburgh Poor Players from September 20 - October 13, 1973 at the University and City Ministries. Photograph is of William Beck and John Kirch.
  - Marathon '33, 1987; 1.0 photograph
    Marathon '33 was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from February 6-14, 1987 at the Kresge Theatre. This photograph is of Dody Fogel and Delbert Highlands.
  - The Marquis de Sade's Justine, 1978; 3.0 photographs
    The Marquis de Sade's Justine was presented by the Theatre Express from April 29 - May 12, 1978 at the Chatham College Chapel. Photographs are of Randell Haynes, James Edmondson, Charles Hall, Dane Snodgrass, and Jocelyn Johnson.
  - A Marriage Proposal, March 1997; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Paul Johns, Summer Shirey, and Ryan Stroup. This Community College of Allegheny County production was performed from March 20 - 22, 1997 at the Boyce Campus Theatre.
  - Marvin's Room, 1999; 2.0 photographs
    Marvin's Room was presented by Mountain Playhouse from September 8-19, 1999. Photograph is of Tracey Moore, Mimi Bessette, Chris Walker, and Stephen Davis.
  - Mass Appeal - Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    Mass Appeal was presented by Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from April 27 - May 26, 1984. Photograph is of Robert Toperzer and Jeff Paul.
  - Mass Appeal - South Park Conservatory Theatre, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    Mass Appeal was presented by the South Park Conservatory Theatre from July 6-22, 1984. Photograph is of Geoffrey Glover and K.V. "Bud" Mellott.
  - Mazel, 2006; 16.0 photographs (on CD-R disc)
    This file contains a CD-R disc with 16 images from Amy Hartman's Mazel. This world premiere production was presented by the Holocaust Center of the United Jewish Federation and the Jewish Theatre of Pittsburgh. The play was performed at the Katz Center for the Performing Arts at the Jewish Community Center of Greater Pittsburgh, November 11th through December 3rd, 2006.
  - Me and My Girl, 1992; 5.0 photographs
    Me and My Girl was presented by Civic Light Opera from June 23-28, 1992. Photographs are of James Brennan, Judy Blazer, and cast.
  - The Merchant of Venice, 1994; 3.0 photograph
    Photographs are from the Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival production of the Merchant of Venice. It was performed at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre May 27th through June 11th, 1994. Appearing in the photos are Laura Ann Worthen as Portia, Brian Rose as Shylock, Brian Byrnes as Salerio, Michael Hartnett as Solanio, and John Neville-Andrews as Antonio. The photographer was Kimberly Pasko.
  - Merrily We Roll Along, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Carol Hickey, Vaughn A. Challingsworth, and Tom Protulipac. This Point Park College Theatre Company production was performed at the Playhouse of Point Park College.
  - Merton of the Movies, 1982; 2.0 photographs
    Merton of the Movies was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from February 25 - March 6, 1982 at the Kresge Theatre. These photographs are of cast members, Robin Slade and Wiley M. Kidd Jr., and composer, Gary Friedman, at rehearsals.
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream - Pittsburgh Metropolitan Stage Company, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    A Midsummer Night's Dream was presented by the Pittsburgh Metropolitan Stage Company from May 28 - June 21, 1981. Photograph is of Charles Waxburg and Matthew Vaky.
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream - Robert Morris College, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    A Midsummer Night's Dream was presented by Robert Morris College from November 12 - 21, 1981. Photograph is of John Roell and Karen Kownacki.
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream: The Musical, 2.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Anne Kittredge and Rodger Cox. This Carnegie Mellon University Repertory Theatre production was performed at Hartwood Acres.
  - The Mikado, 2001; 4.0 photographs
    The Pittsburgh Savoyards presented the Mikado at The Andrew Carnegie Carnegie Free Library Music Hall in Carnegie, PA. The play was performed September 28th through October 14th, 2001. Actors Peter Kant, Christy Marley, Jamie Harper,Sean Johnston, Bill Bluemle, Meighan Lloyd, Kevin Granville, Tom Porter, and Elizabeth Sederburg appear in the photos along with several other members of the cast. Photos by Greg Kornides.
  - Misalliance, 1984; 2.0 photographs
    Misalliance was presented by the Pittsburgh Public Theater from November 20 - December 23, 1984. Photographs are of Drew Keil and Stephanie Dunnam.
  - Miss Evers' Boys, 1992; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Jonas Chaney, Monica Farrell, Douglas Rees, and Ron McClelland. This City Theatre Company production was performed from February 18 - March 15, 1992.
  - Miss Reardon, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    Miss Reardon was presented by the White Barn Theatre from July 13-24, 1976. Photograph is of Jayne Fitzmartin and Jack Keely.
  - Mister Roberts, 1979; 3.0 photographs
    Mister Roberts was presented by the Pittsburgh Public Theater from September 26 - November 4, 1979. Photographs are of John Going (Director), Jon Carpenter, John Newton, Larry Pine, Eileen Maxfed, and Steve Simpson.
  - Moon Over Buffalo, 1997; 1.0 photograph
    Moon Over Buffalo was presented by Mountain Playhouse from August 19-31, 1997. Photograph is of Judy Baird and Douglas Rees.
  - Moonlight, October 1999; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Gina Preciado, Rajest Bose, and Martin Giles. This City Theatre Company production was performed from October 13 - 31, 1999 at the City Theatre.
  - Mother Courage, 2007; 3.0 photographs (on CD-R disc)
    These photographs are of the Pittsburgh Playhouse Repertory Company's production of Bertolt Brecht's Mother Courage. The play was performed March 14th through April 1st, 2007. The images include actors Laurie Klatscher, Randy Kovitz, and Mikelle Johnson.
  - Move Over Mrs. Markham, 1995; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of David Garwood, Tamara Baron, and Joan Decker. This Mount Playhouse production was performed from August 22 - September 3, 1995.
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 3.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Brittney Sweeney, Brian Ferdman, David Lillich, Amy Voigt, and Misty Wilds. This Point Park College Theatre Company production was performed at the Playhouse of Point Park College.
  - The Music Man - Byham, March 1998; 3.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Chuck Aber, David Gookin, Jr., Eliza Chetlin, and Bernard Balbot. This Gargaro Production was performed from March 11 - 17, 1998 at the Byham Theatre.
  - My Fair Lady - Community College of Allegheny College, 1986; 2.0 photographs
    My Fair Lady was presented by the Community College of Allegheny County from July 16-31, 1986. Photographs are of John Roell, J.R. Hall, and Mary Brady.
  - My Fair Lady - Mountain Playhouse, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    My Fair Lady was presented by Mountain Playhouse from July 6 - August 1, 1982. Photograph is of Bob Rizzo and Shannon Lee.
  - My Fair Lady - Plaza Theatre, 1977; 1.0 photograph
    My Fair Lady was presented by Camelot Productions from January 28 - February 20, 1977 at the Plaza Theatre. This photograph shows Linda Johnson.
  - My Three Angels, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    My Three Angels was presented by Mountain Playhouse from August 10-22, 1993. Photograph is of Debbie Damp, Fred Barrows, Frank Mastrone, and Nick Ruggeri.
  - My Way, 2002; 1.0 photograph
    My Way was presented by Mountain Playhouse from October 2-13, 2002. Photograph is of cast members Abe Reybold, Janet Dickinson, Michael Justis, and Jenn Morse.
  - Natalie Needs a Nightie, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Natalie Needs a Necktie was presented by Mountain Playhouse from June 28 - July 10, 1983. Photograph is of David Anthony and Karen Lamb.
  - The Nearlyweds, 1980; 2.0 photographs
    This folder contains two photographs of the East-West International Dinner Theatre's production of The Nearlyweds including Ellen Teets, Betty Tolbert, and Ron Morelli.
  - Never Too Late, 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Fort Pitt Inn Dinner Theatre's production of Never Too Late including Jeff Liebman, Mary Pattison, Ed Sipes, and Karen Kownacki.
  - Nice People Dancing to Good Country Music, 1994; 1.0 photograph
    Nice People Dancing to Good Country Music was presented by the South Park Conservatory Theatre from June 10-26, 1994. Photograph is of Shelby Wyzykowski, Nora Joel, Justin Zeon, Gus Melis, and Joe Dempsey.
  - Night of the Iguana, 1990; 3.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Marco St. John, Sheriden Thomas, Larry John Meyers, and Helena Ruoti. This Pittsburgh Public Theater production was performed from September 27 - November 4, 1990 at the O'Reilly Theater.
  - 'night Mother, 1984; 3.0 photographs
    'night Mother was presented by the Pittsburgh Public Theater from September 25 - October 28, 1984. Photographs are of Sonja Lanzener and Sylvia Sidney.
  - The Normal Heart, 1988; 1.0 photograph
    The Normal Heart was presented by the Pittsburgh Public Theater from April 12 - May 15, 1988. Photograph is of William Rhys and Jim Abele.
  - Not Tonight, I Have a Headache, 1977; 2.0 photographs
    This Don Brockett production, starring Joe Franze and Phyllis Stern, opened at the Ben Gross Restaurant July 14th, 1977.
  - Nunsense, 2.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Judy Baird, Patti Whipple, Pat Van Over, Caitlen Larsen, and Janet Dickinson. Nunsense was performed at the Mountain Playhouse as the final performance for the 1991 season and for the opening performance for the 1992 season.
  - Nunsense, 1999; 1.0 photograph
    Nunsense was presented by the Mountain Playhouse from October 5-17, 1999. Photograph is of Sharon DiCostanzo, Lanen Charters, Mimi Bessett, Tracey Moore, and Michelle Millerick.
  - Nunsense A-Men!, 3.0 photographs
    Photographs are of cast members. This Gargaro Production was performed from December 16, 1998 - January 3, 1999 at Carlow College's Antonian Theatre.
  - Nunsense II: The Second Coming, 1994; 2.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Joe Deer (Director), Celeste Mancinelli, Pat Van Over, Patti Whipple, Janet Dickinson, and Caitlin Larsen. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from May 21 - June 12, 1994.
  - The Odd Couple - Female Version, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    The Odd Couple was presented by the South Park Conservatory Theatre from July 2-18, 1993. Photograph is of Mary Beth Underwood, Wendy Burke, Janet Robb, Patty Cooper, and Lynne Crocco.
  - Of Mice and Men, 2001; 1.0 photograph
    Of Mice and Men was presented by Mountain Playhouse from September 19-30, 2001. This photograph is of Nick Ruggeri and Douglas Rees.
  - Oh Dad, Poor Dad, Mama's Hung You in the Closet and I'm Feeling Sad, 1979; 1.0 photograph
    Oh Dad, Poor Dad, Mama's Hung You in the Closet and I'm Feeling Sad was presented by the White Barn Theatre from July 31 - August 4, 1979. Photograph is of Alice Engleman and Tom Crone.
  - Oklahoma! - Community College of Allegheny County, 1992; 1.0 photograph
    This photograph shows actors Larry Newman as Will Parker, Mary Brady as Ado Annie, and Joe Milliren as Ali Hakim in Oklahoma!. The Community College of Allegheny County production was performed at the South campus from July 17th through August 1st, 1992.
  - Oklahoma! - Mountain Playhouse, 1967; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Jo Henderson and Larry Payne. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed in 1967.
  - Oklahoma! - Mountain Playhouse, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    Oklahoma! was presented at the Mountain Playhouse in 1980. This photograph is of Mary Ellen Richardson and Bill Milvaney.
  - Oklahoma! - Mountain Playhouse, 1991; 2.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Janet Dickinson, Michael Carrigan, Suzanne Hawe, and Dean Stroop. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from July 9 - August 4, 1991.
  - Oliver! - Civic Light Opera, 1992; 1.0 photograph
    Oliver! was presented by Civic Light Opera from July 21-26, 1992. Photograph is of Jon Cypher and Jim Hall.
  - Oliver! - McKeesport Little Theater, 1980; 1.0 photograph
    Oliver! was presented by the McKeesport Little Theater from September 12 - October 12, 1980. Photograph is of Don Berns and James Valecko.
  - Oliver! - Mountain Playhouse, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    Oliver! was presented by Mountain Playhouse from July 13 - August 8, 1993. Photograph is of Janet Dickinson and Jim Hall.
  - On Golden Pond, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    On Golden Pond was presented by Mountain Playhouse from September 16-27, 1981. Photograph is of Paul Lagrez and Charles Crain.
  - Once Upon a Mattress, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    Once Upon a Mattress was presented by Civic Light Opera from July 17-22, 1984. Photograph is of Rose Marie, Morey Amsterdam, and Lenora Nemetz.
  - Once Upon a Tale, 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Schooltime Theatre's production of Once Upon a Tale including Curtis Booker as Mr Pulitzer, Mary Beth Kayson as Nellie Bly, and Julie Silverman as Annie O'Toole.
  - The Opera Around the World, October 1975; 1.0 photograph
    The Opera Around the World was a dinner opera that was staged at the Holiday Inn, New Castle on October 25, 1975. The Lyric Opera Theatre production was directed by and featured Claudia Pinza. Photograph is a collage of several of the performers.
  - Ophelia, 1992; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is from the Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival's Young Company's production of Ophelia. The play was a joint production between the Young Company and the NOHO Company. It was performed at the Pit Theatre in Oakland from June 19th through July 11th, 1992. Appearing in the photo are Candice Brown-McDonald as Ophelia and Kinneret Noy as Doubt. The photographer was Ric Evans.
  - The Oresteia, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Kenneth Roberts and Patricia Miles. This University of Pittsburgh Theatre production was performed at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre.
  - Orphans, 1987; 1.0 photograph
    Orphans was presented by the Pittsburgh Public Theater from January 6 - February 8, 1987. Photograph is of Stephen Mailer and James Anthony Shanta.
  - Our Country's Good, 1992; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Dee Pelletier, Kelley Panczyk, Nona Gerard, Doug Rees, Dan Frezza, Don Marshall, and Mark Thompson. This City Theatre Company production was performed from May 12 - June 7, 1992
  - Out Cry, 1977; 1.0 photograph
    Out Cry was presented by the Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from January 20 - February 27, 1977. Photograph is of Bingo O'Malley.
  - Out of Order, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    Out of Order was presented by Mountain Playhouse from August 24 - September 5, 1993. Photograph is of cast members, Debbie Damp, Janet Dickinson, David Garwood, Patti Whipple, Nick Ruggeri, Lee Brock, Neil Young, Mitchell Kantor, Matthew Marafino, and Frank Mastrone.
  - Over the Tavern - Mountain Playhouse, 1998; 1.0 photograph
    Over the Tavern was presented by Mountain Playhouse from June 16-28, 1998. Photograph is of Margaret Goodman and Chirs Walker.
  - Over the Tavern - Pittsburgh Public Theater, 1996; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Judith K. Hart and Bill Cwikowski. This Pittsburgh Public Theater production was performed from November 21 - December 29, 1996.
  - The Owl and the Pussycat, 1975; 1.0 photograph
    The Owl and the Pussycat was presented by the White Barn Theatre in August, 1975. Photograph is of Barbara McCloy and Ken Miller.
  - P.S. Your Cat is Dead, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of The Winter Company's production of P.S. Your Cat is Dead at Chatham College including Mark Tierno.
  - Painting Churches, 1986; 1.0 photograph
    Painting Churches was presented by City Theatre from February 27 - March 29, 1986. Photograph is of Denise Huot, Bingo O'Malley, and Kelly Maurer.
  - Pajama Game - Civic Light Opera, July 1957; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Justine Johnston, Thelma Pelish, and Coley Worth. This Civic Light Opera production was performed from July 8 - July 13, 1957 at the Pitt Stadium.
  - Pajama Game - Oliver Plaza Dinner Theatre, Oct. 30, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Betty Caplan Productions The Pajama Game at Oliver Plaza Dinner Theatre.
  - Pajama Game - White Barn Theatre, 1980; 1.0 photograph
    Pajama Game was presented by the White Barn Theatre from September 19 - October 11, 1980. Photograph is of Jack Kelly and George Eisenhauer.
  - Paint Your Wagon, 1993; 1.0 photograph